Abdulaziz Kheder Alghamdi

- ★ Abdulaziz0khadr@hotmail.com
- 📞 0536633085 🛮 in Abdulaziz Alghamdi
- ► Saudi Jeddah ## 27/04/2001

Summary

Computer Science Student with progressive experience writing code and designing solutions. Excited to be part of a team to learn and improve my knowledge

Programing languages

Java

Python

Skills

Teamwork, Leadership, Problem solving, Creative thinking, Communication, Presentation

Education

FCIT / Computer Science,

King Abdulaziz University

□

2019 – present | Jeddah, Saudi Arabia

Awards

Certificate of Excellence,

King Abdulaziz University ☐ 2020

A certificate is given to student who succeeds in achieving a GPA of 4.5 and above in successive semesters in the academic year

Certificate of Excellence,

King Abdulaziz University

2022

A certificate is given to student who succeeds in achieving a GPA of 4.5 and above in successive semesters in the academic year

Introduction to Artificial Intelligence

Bootcamp, KAUST Academy □

2023

5 days Bootcamp about Artificial Intelligence and Machin Learning using Python

Advanced Artificial Intelligence Bootcamp,

KAUST Academy ☑

2023

4 days Bootcamp of learning advanced topics in artificial intelligence and computer vision using Python

Work experience

Captain, Careem

2022 – present | Jeddah, Saudi Arabia

Mrsool, Mrsool ☑

2021 | Jeddah, Saudi Arabia

Sales manager, Istraht Al-sitan

2017 - 2019 | Jeddah, Saudi Arabia

Volunteering

Ministry of National Guard Health Affairs

(MNG-HA), Organizer ☑

2021 | Jeddah, Saudi Arabia